(Penny:)Excuse me.
(Sheldon:)I've been studying how
to make people laugh.
(Sheldon:)They say that comedy
is tragedy plus time.
(Sheldon:)-Let's tickle some ribs.
-No!
(Penny(on phone):)No, Dad, I don't think they
cut me out of the show
(Penny(on phone):)because I was too pretty.
(Penny(on phone):)No, I don't need you to come out
and kick Mark Harmon's ass.
(Penny(on phone):)Daddy, I gotta go.
I love you. Bye.
(Leonard:)-How you doing?
-(GROANS) This is such a disaster.
(Penny:)My parents had all my relatives over.
(Penny:)They got one of those
six-foot sandwiches,
(Penny:)and got my brother
a day pass out of rehab and...
(Penny:)...now he's missing
and the sandwich is missing, and...
(Penny:)They're probably in Mexico by now.
So humiliating.